Metal up your ass.
Metal Lords is a comedy, drama, music film directed by Peter Sollett.
For teenage misfits Hunter and Kevin, the path to glory
is clear: Devote themselves to metal.
Win Battle of the Bands.
And be worshipped like gods.
Kevin Schlieb, played by Jaeden Martell.
Hunter Sylvester, played by Adrian Greensmith.
Emily Spector, played by Isis Hainsworth.
Clay Moss, played by Noah Urrea.
Dr. Sylvester, played by Brett Gelman.
Kendall Sarn, played by Analesa Fisher.
Metal Lords is a 2022 American teen comedy-drama film written by D.
Weiss and directed by Peter Sollett.
The story follows two high school best friends and metal music lovers, Hunter and
Kevin, who set out to start a metal band, against societal norms.
Notably, the renowned guitarist Tom Morello was an executive producer
and wrote some of the songs performed in the film.
The film was released on Netflix on April 8, 2022.
The film explores themes of high school, heavy
metal, high school band, music, amused.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.